<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Half a smoke</title>
    <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Half a smoke</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us vi</language>
    <copyright>halfasmoke</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 22:45:46 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title># collection no.2</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/31-aug-collection-no2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 22:45:46 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/31-aug-collection-no2/</guid>
      <description>-
you are a mirror, when i look into you and stare at your soul. i know and learn to love myself&amp;hellip;
&amp;ndash;
it’s all scatter everywhere, a mess
and all of this are nothing but scatter pieces
no beginning nor ending
even a puzzle have collected pieces
a place for each piece,
meant to be in that place
&amp;ndash;
if one person doens&amp;rsquo;t have those thoughts anymore, would them still be the same person?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># the hill</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/29-aug-down-up-hill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:54:10 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/29-aug-down-up-hill/</guid>
      <description>-
It all began on top of the hill, excited and fun, and slowly slided down until they reached the ‘valley of despair’ where all they can see is nothing but fog, mist, dark, and not everyone can get out of it, hence the name.
But those who keep rolling despite the heavy baggage, the string, pulling them back, those who have strength, courage will see the end of it, that is, a glimpse of hope in the form of a light beam shining down on their path.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># sleeping act</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/28-aug-sleeping-act/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 22:40:56 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/28-aug-sleeping-act/</guid>
      <description>-
He was laying, turning his body around and around to find a comfortable position to sleep. Yesterday he slept like a snail, curled everything up, the day before, a vampire, with both his arms and legs straight out, and the day before that, a butterfly, tomorrow maybe a giraffe, standing. Every time he found it, he only had one wish.
He wishes to have a bullet fired through his head to make them stop running or a sword pierced through his heart to make it stop feeling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># suddenly</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/25-aug-suddenly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 22:40:06 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/25-aug-suddenly/</guid>
      <description>-
Childhood isn&amp;rsquo;t in some of those photographs, isn&amp;rsquo;t in those places you used to visit. It is when a familiar aroma suddenly hits your nose that makes you remember your mother&amp;rsquo;s breakfast, a familiar scent of the newly built house that makes you remember going out with your father to buy cement for your new home. A sudden scene of those kids playing with dirt makes you remember when you sneaked out to catch crickets with your friends at night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># two windows</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/23-aug-two-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 22:58:23 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/23-aug-two-windows/</guid>
      <description>-
time like this, usually they have two windows, one to see out side and another to the world.
and those who that don&amp;rsquo;t have the latter, they carry themselves with a vivid imagination. with only a tree, they can tell others stories, and with only one beam of light, they can see the sun.
they must be the strongest of all to make it through this time of life, but will those imagination ever stop running, and creating such lively images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># another attempt</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/22-aug-another-attempt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 22:38:39 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/22-aug-another-attempt/</guid>
      <description>-
When there is no solution yet to be found, escapism will become king, a cruel one. But one will not see the king at first hand, his loyal servant - &amp;lsquo;denial&amp;rsquo; will stand at the gate, perhaps, ready for a fight if one persists in meeting a king.
All that to the question: what will the king do?
If one has the strength and courage to defeat such “a being”, a hidden door behind his throne will lead one to freedom, liberation, and clarity as well as stillness in one’s mind - become the hero in the midst of ordinary with power to create the extraordinary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># the dance</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/21-aug-the-dance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 22:56:09 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/21-aug-the-dance/</guid>
      <description>-
one time we had a dance
maybe you think that was nothing
and maybe that was by chance
but i remember it despite my bad memory
every footstep, backward and forward
in every note of that song
but i guess i was late
alone, i have to solve this crossword
this is no Careless whisper
but the tune sings loudly in my head
maybe in the bleak midwinter
i’ll play the song again on my old cassette</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># wears off</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/18-aug-2021-wears-off/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 20:43:33 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/18-aug-2021-wears-off/</guid>
      <description>-
Suppose you came back from where that took something from you or everything. The one who came back was not the one who walked in and what after that is just some extra time that they gave to you.
Some may take that time and do something crazy or stupid, some may take it to create the extraordinary or close to the extraordinary. Either way, it isn&amp;rsquo;t bad if you look at it, they all prepare to immerse themselves in the nothingness, that is, death.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># different</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/15-aug-2021-different/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 23:40:08 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/15-aug-2021-different/</guid>
      <description>-
I am a picture but try telling a story
You are a story but try painting an album
We are living in the same world
But seem to be from two different one
Is it funny, isn&amp;rsquo;t it?
Just like
small lizard in the rain
oh how did he get there
with the house he&amp;rsquo;s been crawling on
cannot seem to find a home
with all the food he&amp;rsquo;s been stepping on</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># mirror</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/12-aug-2021-mirror/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 21:43:52 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/12-aug-2021-mirror/</guid>
      <description>-
a child stops smiling
a woman goes silence
a man never came back
the wind, raging, yelling
the cloud, pouring down the soil
the moon, turned dark
teardrops, swallowed the sun
the bird, now swimming
fingers, turned into matches
water, turned into oxygen
and ignited its very own soul
but there&amp;rsquo;s still another side of the mirror
and the sky is pretty much blue over here&amp;hellip;
 &amp;ldquo;mọi chuyện dường như quá đỗi bình thường&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># i don&#39;t know</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/12-aug-2021-i-dont-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 18:08:16 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/12-aug-2021-i-dont-know/</guid>
      <description>-
there are a lot of words to be said but none shall hear for all she ever did was write them down in that paper sheet and burn it afterwards.
those ashes&amp;hellip;flying, flowing mid-air, circling around her as if they are singing to her ears, and saying those words back to her, telling her own stories.
that is a ritual she loves to do when her voice cracks, her throat thickens, and when she is all by herself, and when she types the last word of each page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># anew</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/11-aug-2021-anew/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 21:46:47 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/11-aug-2021-anew/</guid>
      <description>-
&amp;ldquo;If only you could answer,
If only your heart had courage to lift itself up and take a chance.
The promise of luminous eyes,
Beyond the dark curtain of my hollow soul&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
why does oneself can see such a beautiful thing?
maybe because now, in one&amp;rsquo;s mind, something has opened, and something has awaken&amp;hellip;
or it&amp;rsquo;s already there to be read.
the bridge has once again, presented
hopefully, it won&amp;rsquo;t blow up halfway through&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># collection no.1</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/10-aug-2021-collection-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 21:51:29 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/10-aug-2021-collection-one/</guid>
      <description>-
&amp;ndash;
Ever wonder that film, music, and books are made to sympathize your feeling that your person could not?
&amp;ndash;
Suppose you made a deal with a demon to exchange your soul for some incredible power.
But it would be funny if someone want a soul in exchange for its incredible power&amp;hellip; Can a demon capable of doing such thing?
&amp;ndash;
&amp;ldquo;That era has passed.
Nothing that belonged to it exists anymore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># story and picture</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/06-aug-2021-story-and-picture/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 21:58:06 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/06-aug-2021-story-and-picture/</guid>
      <description>-
telling a story is like painting a picture.
starting with a simple point, then a line, sometimes a curve, adding colour, favorite colour, good one, bad one just to make it diverse.
some may call it good, some may add a few details, and some may even tear the whole canvas apart. but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter because paint can be drawn again, all the line, the curve, the detail are already there, and the original exists nowhere else but within the painter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># a heart-less</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/05-aug-2021-a-heart-less/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 18:10:58 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/05-aug-2021-a-heart-less/</guid>
      <description>-
A man was taking a stroll after dinner as usual then saw a small bar with an interesting name and decided to go in. The bar seems amusing but strangely no one there but the owner.
He sat down at the counter. After a few drinks, he told the bartender
“You know what would be funny? It’s able to take your heart out, hold it in your hand and see it beating slowly, but the mind thinks it already died a long time ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># shadow people</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/03-aug-2021-shadow-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 22:02:38 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/03-aug-2021-shadow-people/</guid>
      <description>-
all are but shadows, can only be seen at days, return home and emrged at night.
conceal behind one&amp;rsquo;s back, a place only for the second, and let out a cry when light outs.
they are always there even if the flames are not&amp;hellip; so don&amp;rsquo;t be afraid.
 &amp;ldquo;mọi chuyện dường như quá đỗi bình thường&amp;rdquo;
-R</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># away it goes</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/03-aug-2021-away-it-goes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 18:38:59 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/03-aug-2021-away-it-goes/</guid>
      <description>-
There it goes, away it goes
The day goes by and something talking with nothing
Maybe expecting plays out too much
Maybe hope is persevering
A little jazz playing there
A little blue in this bottle
A little fish swimming slowly
The old train forgot direction to the castle
Angel wings are dropping, so seemingly
&amp;lsquo;Chet Baker - Almost blue&amp;rsquo;
Wind sticks to the wall like glue
‘In the mood for love - Shigeru Umebayashi’</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># on a bridge</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/02-aug-2021-on-a-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 22:04:44 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/02-aug-2021-on-a-bridge/</guid>
      <description>-
i was falling from my rope while everyone else was climbing their own.
upon landing, at the pit, lost and confused, i saw the rope, one single hanging rope, not sure where this will lead to but climb it anyway.
hopefully it will reach &amp;ldquo;the top&amp;rdquo;
 &amp;ldquo;mọi chuyện dường như quá đỗi bình thường&amp;rdquo;
-R</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># supine</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/02-aug-2021-supine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 18:40:43 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/02-aug-2021-supine/</guid>
      <description>-
Everyday is the same, he follows a structure, a pattern which he knows perfectly well, as if he pushes a stone up a mountain just to see the stone rolls down and tomorrow will be the same, rarely a peak of joyfulness but that surely keeps his soul intact.
He seems to have things which anyone will find contentment ?
 &amp;ldquo;mọi chuyện dường như quá đỗi bình thường&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># untitled no.2</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/31-jul-2021-untitled-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 22:07:40 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/31-jul-2021-untitled-2/</guid>
      <description>-
it&amp;rsquo;s sure the world keeps the moon in the sky,
and the sun deeps in the ocean.
but the moon is no more,
the sun has let out its last light beam,
only eternal darkness growing, rapidly.
but what is darkness without light
maybe light itself is just darkness in disguise
to give them a false sense of hope,
that is,
tomorrow is a new day,
yesterday was a mistake,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># beauty and sadness</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/30-jul-2021-beauty-and-sadness/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 18:42:35 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/30-jul-2021-beauty-and-sadness/</guid>
      <description>-
the term “just for fun” implied the existence of “just for sad”
Suppose one day, you go to the mountain just to sit down, watch the sky, and observe.
Spot a lonely tree has its root deep into the soil of an isolated hill - feel the sadness just for the sake of it.
Spot a solo flying bird and a single beam of sunlight shining over it as if it was guidance to the nest - feel the sadness just for the sake of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># arise</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/30-jul-2021-arise/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 18:41:32 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/30-jul-2021-arise/</guid>
      <description>-
I don&amp;rsquo;t see you anymore
The walls start talking again
&amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s alright, let them come&amp;rdquo;
I don&amp;rsquo;t hear your voice anymore
The night is still quiet again
&amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s alright, let it be&amp;rdquo;
Oh you, young boy
Where are you, why do you have to sink that low?
The boy who keep saying &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s alright&amp;rdquo; to me
Nothing but silence now
Guess I have to say it to myself
And the old dance routine at midnight</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># a quiet night</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/29-jul-2021-quiet-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 22:14:06 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/29-jul-2021-quiet-night/</guid>
      <description>-
it’s quiet the night
i can hear the cricket
it’s quiet the night
i can hear raindrop in my head
it’s quiet the night
i can hear my skin shedding
it’s quiet the night
i can hear my bone cracking
it’s quiet the night
i can hear my heartbeat
it’s quiet the night
i can hear footsteps out in the street
it’s quiet the night
i can hear the walls again</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># video game</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/29-jul-2021-video-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 18:43:52 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/29-jul-2021-video-game/</guid>
      <description>-
Life is brilliant. Beautiful. It enchants us, to the point of obsession.
Some are true to their purpose, though they are but shells, flesh and mind.
One man lost his own body, but lingered on, as a head.
Others chase the charms of love, however elusive.
Peace grants men the illusion of life.
Shackled by falsehoods, they yearn for love, unaware of its grand illusion.
Until, the curse touches their flesh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># mediocre-ish</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/28-jul-2021-mediocre/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 18:45:50 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/28-jul-2021-mediocre/</guid>
      <description>-
Watching some extraordinary film to feel less ordinary, when that two hours of goodness ended, the train takes you back to your homeland. Everything you do is too normal to the point that makes you hate it, but that’s not the end, living with the thing you hate turned out that you slowly love them.
And from that moment on, you don’t have to revolt against it anymore, it has become your greatest ally that no person in the world could match its strengths or even weaknesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># untitled no.3</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/23-jul-2021-untitled-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 22:19:55 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/23-jul-2021-untitled-3/</guid>
      <description>-
far too complex to describe
far too difficult to say out loud.
a man smoking cigarette at midnight,
a woman wishing by the lake,
a child went silent.
art using it&amp;rsquo;s abstract strokes,
a song blending its note variation.
an old couple sitting on park bench,
a young couple holding hands,
and a person hanging themselves.
try, they all did
as if giving all of those a shape that words could not</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># forgot</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/22-jul-2021-forgot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 22:43:12 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/22-jul-2021-forgot/</guid>
      <description>-
forgot how to run
forgot how to walk
forgot how to sing
forgot how to talk
forgot how to touch
forgot how to hold
forgot how to hug
forgot how to let go
forgot how to say “goodbye”
forgot how to say “hello”
forgot how to smile
forgot how to frown
this is not something profound
this is just something to remember
remember the adventure
and remember to send her</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># wandering soul</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/20-jul-2021-wandering-soul/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 22:44:28 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/20-jul-2021-wandering-soul/</guid>
      <description>-
In endless realm of nothingness, obscure darkness
Exists something ethereal, unfathomable yet seemingly wondrous
Soul
Floating mindlessly, and…
One found another amongst the many
Stumbled upon each others
Somehow, in some way miraculously and strangely
Regardless
Let those unify
Resonate in frequency, echo through eternity
Then let those wander in the midst of stars
Delicately
Circling around the sun, dallying
Delight in the warmth, the golden gleam
Tastefulness in all between</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># to drink</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/19-jul-2021-to-drink/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 23:02:54 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/19-jul-2021-to-drink/</guid>
      <description>-
to drink is
to forget something
to remember something
to make something happen
to wish of undone something
to feel what word failed to say
and to see what action failed to do
drink once to this
drink twice to that
drink finite to the infinite
 &amp;ldquo;mọi chuyện dường như quá đỗi bình thường&amp;rdquo;
-R</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># the rare</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/19-jul-2021-the-rare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 22:48:22 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/19-jul-2021-the-rare/</guid>
      <description>-
The rare is indeed for the rare
But is it wrong to change one&amp;rsquo;s surroundings? one always have the power to do as such
It could be the way one&amp;rsquo;s trust is different and the way one choose to filter out the rare
One might encounter some might be glad to water the soil, or even poison the air, but that’s the risk one is willing to take, isn&amp;rsquo;t it so?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># do this</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/17-jul-2021-do-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2021 23:18:40 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/17-jul-2021-do-this/</guid>
      <description>-
If you wanna swim in the ocean of laughter, do this
but be careful for the regretting shark
If you wanna unlock the hidden memories, do this
but be careful ‘cause there’s no guidance
If you wanna see how much you’ve grown, do this
but be careful for your own ignorance
If you wanna feel something other than nothing, do this
but be careful for the rabbit, do not chase the rabbit</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># beautiful</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/17-jul-2021-beautiful/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2021 23:06:30 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/17-jul-2021-beautiful/</guid>
      <description>-
what makes something bearutiful? is it the existence of the opposite - ugly?
but then what makes the thing ugly or unpleasant?
or is it always a beauty that exists in the observer&amp;rsquo;s eyes?
never seen the face never seen the smile
just a glimpse
not eyes but only one
enough to say
&amp;ldquo;Ah, beauty&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
eh?
 &amp;ldquo;mọi chuyện dường như quá đỗi bình thường&amp;rdquo;
-R</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># illusion of freedom</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/16-jul-2021-illusion-of-freedom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 13:05:01 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/16-jul-2021-illusion-of-freedom/</guid>
      <description>-
Longing for freedom
the one that allows us to fully express ourselves, to the endless sky, soaring with the wind, absorbing the warm sunlight, to emerge oneself with the earth, liberation
like a kite, flying with all of its wills
But it is all but an illusion for a kite has a string
A string help it fly, and at some point, will pull it back, put in a closet</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># roses</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/14-jul-2021-roses/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 14:35:46 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/14-jul-2021-roses/</guid>
      <description>-
he saw it many times but this time, he had it, held it only to be pricked by its thorns and given a warning not to come near&amp;hellip;
he can only watch from afar now
Watching it bloom with all of its flawless beauty in the dawn, letting sunlight slips through its petals delicately
&amp;hellip;and so the thought, maybe he is this way, maybe just to observe, maybe a watcher, a mere audience sometimes feels warm in his chest and silently enrichs the soil</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># apathy</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/14-jul-2021-apathy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 13:03:56 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/14-jul-2021-apathy/</guid>
      <description>-
a tale of a king who tried to conquer death
a mighty emperor, a fearless conqueror
his fortune is massive, no one has ever heard of his name
some may say the whole world is at his disposal
but one thing still scares him every day of his life - death
that is, one day he will eventually leave everything behind
so he tries many attempts to conquer death</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># resemblance</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/13-jul-2021-resemblance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 13:02:55 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/13-jul-2021-resemblance/</guid>
      <description>-
it began as a mistake…
a corpse
Lying in the field with nothing but the dust blowing wind and sometimes the smell of burning nearby friends
Was he the bartender pouring his drink last night?
Was she the woman who slapped him last night?
Couldn’t remember, because&amp;hellip;
Alive every sunshine but each is a different character and a different world and in each of which, he must die.
Last night was a pirate, drowned, the day before was a cheerful old grandma, died of old age&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># madness</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/12-jul-2021-madness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 14:27:20 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/12-jul-2021-madness/</guid>
      <description>-
I.
They have four horsemen of apocalypse He has four walls of contemplation 3 days ago, he named this wall Dabria
2 days ago, he named this Aeron
Yesterday, he named this one Brona
If it wasn&amp;rsquo;t for you, he would&amp;rsquo;ve named the last one Sterben
If it wasn&amp;rsquo;t for you, he would&amp;rsquo;ve named the last one Tom
If it wasn&amp;rsquo;t for you, he would descended to madness
If it wasn&amp;rsquo;t for you, he would pulled the trigger</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># a moment of freedom</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/11-jul-2021-moment-of-freedom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 14:18:24 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/11-jul-2021-moment-of-freedom/</guid>
      <description>-
a man with a boat in the middle of the lake is an act of freedom
slowly rowing his boat aimlessly in the midst of waves,
not necessarily knowing where to but in the man&amp;rsquo;s mind,
he knows exactly where the destination is,
solely because it is his boat.
not necessarily requiring companion or friend,
he knows exactly how to keep him sane,
solely because he himself, is at peace,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># the Woman</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/07-jul-2021-the-woman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 13:01:52 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/07-jul-2021-the-woman/</guid>
      <description>-
he is a wolf chasing his moon
every night, he howls, hopefully.
climbing mounts and wanting
the moon to be closer.
and one time, drinking water in a lake nearby,
he stumbled upon the moon reflection.
sat down and started gazing at its whiteness beauty
and he singed his favourite song to it,
waves washed on his feet as if the moon is listening to his tunes.
after singing his final note and without hesitation,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># bad Game</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/05-jul-2021-bad-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 13:00:29 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/05-jul-2021-bad-game/</guid>
      <description>-
Link the fire to extend the age of Light or let it fade to introduce the age of men, dark. But in the age of dark, embers will dance, and once again, fire will be rekindled.
But whether to do or not to do, a loop is always created.
A circle that has no end nor beginning, a mere absurdity will bring every action to a halt.
There is no right answer nor there is wrong, it just is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># an answer ? </title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/03-jul-2021-answer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 23:37:12 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/03-jul-2021-answer/</guid>
      <description>-
Going left is only right in some cases and going right is only right in some cases. Whether to choose to go left or right solely depends on the occasion and circumstances.
What if one chooses to stay in the middle and wait for the situation to act, to choose which path, left or right? But choosing to stay is also choosing to go either left or right, in a bigger picture, thus creating infinite paths, infinite choices in one&amp;rsquo;s mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># the secret setrayal</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/01-jul-2021-secret-betrayal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 15:40:15 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/01-jul-2021-secret-betrayal/</guid>
      <description>-
‘Only in truth, the lords will abandon their thrones’
Souls of lords he’s gathered, five lords sit on their five thrones, now the final battle has approached. But he has something that was meant to be hidden, far away from the world, lurking itself in the frightful image of the abandoned realm. The eyes of a Fire Keeper…
‘… but Fire Keepers are not meant to have eyes.
It is forbidden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># the barmaid and the ashen one</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/26-may-2021-barmaid-ashen-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 10:59:33 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/26-may-2021-barmaid-ashen-one/</guid>
      <description>-
barmaid: “Last day, huh?”
ashen one: “I guess so”
barmaid: “Have something to say, don’t you?”
ashen one: “ *sigh * I think I dug myself a hole so deep that now I am lost under the ground, too far down from the surface, worse than that, I’ve been there for too long and the comfort is growing within myself. I no longer long for a way out but at the same time I can sense a tiny fracture of myself screaming, stretching to the sky but all of that, all the effort were in vain and so close to the edge of hopelessness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># untitled</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/20-may-2021-untitled/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 17:03:28 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/20-may-2021-untitled/</guid>
      <description>-
A million voices scream every day, a million voices want to be heard, a million stories want to be told but not a single ear wants to listen, then those screams turned into silence, those stories were forced to cut their own words. Thus, creates a void of stillness like a lake in the bleak winter, with only eyes left to look at one after another, time itself froze at the bottomless lake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># in middle</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/15-jul-2021-in-middle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 23:33:58 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/15-jul-2021-in-middle/</guid>
      <description>-
Tôi tin rằng có một kiểu người như thế này, kiểu người &amp;ldquo;ở giữa&amp;rdquo;, kiểu người tồn tại giữa hai thế giới, không hẳn đã chết nhưng cũng chưa thực sự sống. Thích đèn vàng thay cho đỏ hay xanh, chưa thực sự cười và cũng chưa rơi quá một giọt lệ, có thể thỏa mình trên chuyến đi nhưng lại ghét bắt đầu hay kết thúc nó.
Chỉ có thể tìm đến y trong lúc bạn lưỡng lự nên nhớ hay quên, trong lúc mặt trời sắp lặn, trong lúc nụ cười dần tắt, trong câu trả lời là &amp;ldquo;Bình thường&amp;rdquo; cho câu hỏi &amp;ldquo;Đang vui hay buồn?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># peace of mind</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/10-may-2021-peace-of-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 17:04:19 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/10-may-2021-peace-of-mind/</guid>
      <description>-
He can only find it in between of things, between the honking sound of one car and another, between the ticking second of a traffic light when he looked at it, between the finished task to another beginning, between each sip of coffee and finally between the consolatory silence.
He is in war with no one other than himself, he wants something which cannot exist, his war but in peace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># enough to fill a man&#39;s heart</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/02-may-2021-mans-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 15:06:48 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/02-may-2021-mans-heart/</guid>
      <description>-
A young man who always feels he doesn&amp;rsquo;t belong, every where he went, he felt a sense of disconnect, disconnect with his surrounding, his people, sometimes his mind as if he hungry for a place of his own, his own trees howling in the wind, his own moon&amp;rsquo;s reflection on a quiet lake, his own sun circling around him..his own people.
Everyday he counts his steps while walking to the four walls of contentment, missed one step he thought but it&amp;rsquo;s matter not as he unlocking the door.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># key, room and memories</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/29-apr-2021-key-room-memories/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 15:04:30 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/29-apr-2021-key-room-memories/</guid>
      <description>-
everyday she is granted a key to a room
she went in
one time she was so happy and didn&amp;rsquo;t want to leave
one time she couldn&amp;rsquo;t move even a finger upon entering
one time she was so frightened by all the pictures hanged on the wall
one time she just smiled and left
one time she didn&amp;rsquo;t enter any room, she sat down and looked, looked around, looked inward, inside of her and suddenly around her was filled with&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># knowing</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/20-apr-2021-knowing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 16:52:42 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/20-apr-2021-knowing/</guid>
      <description>-
All this time in my head there was a question, one question can turn everything seems joyful into gloomy, cleverness into sadness and happiness into despair.
I long for an answer, a direction, or simply a guideline to set out&amp;hellip;
as you may guess, I found it, found the answer, THE answer
that is, my effort, my attempt, my endeavor was less than the meaningless and the nothingness itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># the last stranger </title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/05-apr-2021-last-stranger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 13:49:17 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/05-apr-2021-last-stranger/</guid>
      <description>-
𝘢𝘧𝘵𝘦𝘳 𝘢 𝘸𝘩𝘪𝘭𝘦, 𝘣𝘰𝘵𝘩 𝘴𝘢𝘵 𝘥𝘰𝘸𝘯 𝘣𝘺 𝘵𝘩𝘦 𝘭𝘢𝘬𝘦&amp;hellip;
&amp;ldquo;Why are you doing this, searching for the dead, lurking in the dark as if you&amp;rsquo;re trying to achieve something, get something from them?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Memory&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Memory?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m able to do it, to feel more&amp;hellip;alive. Memory is the only real thing to me, they gave me a taste of what I&amp;rsquo;m missing, humanity.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I can still save you, just let me help.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># man in search</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/21-feb-2021-man-in-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 09:26:16 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/21-feb-2021-man-in-search/</guid>
      <description>-
man searching for his soul
&amp;ldquo;who leaves can never return and for those who stay will receive eternal joy&amp;rdquo; that was what he saw at the door when he&amp;rsquo;s pondering on his decision whether to stay or to leave
&amp;ldquo;to fill, must, to break&amp;rdquo; he heard that long ago from an old man and that night, he couldn&amp;rsquo;t sleep, he was thinking but he couldn&amp;rsquo;t say anything, to her</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># story of a man</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/26-jan-2021-man-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 17:34:09 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/26-jan-2021-man-story/</guid>
      <description>-
let me tell you a story about a man
every night he shuts his eyes, he saw himself standing in a room, a space, an area, whatever but there is nothing but himself
and every time he&amp;rsquo;s in there, he was forced to play&amp;hellip;
he played his memories back and forth
he played those pictures as a movie
he played those words as a sentence
he played those tunes as a song</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># silence</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/01-jan-2021-silence/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 09:10:24 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/01-jan-2021-silence/</guid>
      <description>-
I&amp;rsquo;m in a room, that unforgettable room
lighted a cigarette
and they&amp;rsquo;re coming at me, good and bad
it&amp;rsquo;s ok, I want them to
pieces of broken vase, by accident, floating and scratching the air
&amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;don&amp;rsquo;t be sorry&amp;rdquo;
opening a window, too much smoke
sitting up there, contemplating
all the noise, TV, fans, bikes down the street, birds in a room&amp;hellip;?
but I can only hear the silence between them</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># bad dream</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/21-dec-2020-bad-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 07:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/21-dec-2020-bad-dream/</guid>
      <description>-
Đọc lại quyển sổ cũ và thấy trang mà tôi viết về một sự kiện đã qua cho tôi một cảm giác mà tôi không biết dùng từ nào để diễn tả về nó. Cứ như được sống lại trong những kí ức tồi tàn đó, như cơn ác mộng, nhưng đó lại là cơn ác mộng do tôi tự tạo ra, thế nghĩa là gì cơ chứ.
Nhưng dù sao thì mọi chuyện đã qua, giờ chỉ còn là những kí ức khó quên.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># fun Souls</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/14-dec-2020-souls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 15:04:36 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/14-dec-2020-souls/</guid>
      <description>-
In a world where Fire is fundamental&amp;hellip;
There’s a man, the chosen one they called him, carrying out a task&amp;hellip; an old prophecy.
“&amp;hellip;maketh pilgrimage to the land of Ancient Lords…
…When thou ringeth the Bell of Awakening, fate, thou shalt know&amp;hellip;”
Set foot into the land of Ancient lords whose throne forsaken and slowly fall into obscurity. Encountered countless decaying skeletons, senseless undeads, horrendous monsters, even dragons. Fought them all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># self-fulfilling prophecy</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/18-nov-2020-self-fulfilling-prophecy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 15:34:20 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/18-nov-2020-self-fulfilling-prophecy/</guid>
      <description>-
close my eyes
i feel my head hurt, then it stop
i hear my heart pounding, non-stop
i smell a familiar scent
but
i see nothing, bleak black
for i walked into the abyss
alone like everyone else
but&amp;hellip;
with nothing in hands and barefooted
returned
but the man who walked in was never return
no one ever return the same
it got something of us all
it got something</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># the abyss - 1st attemp</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/06-nov-2020-abyss/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 11:34:03 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/06-nov-2020-abyss/</guid>
      <description>-
the greatest challenge of all is not to overcome obstacles or running through some milestones
it is to face oneself in the nothingness, the abyss, to look inward within oneself, to dive deep, to search for what lies underneath not just the tip of the iceberg
because&amp;hellip; the abyss is all around us
suppose one day you&amp;rsquo;re happily strolling in the street or mistakenly counting your steps on a drunken night out</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># khoảnh khắc</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/19-oct-2020-moment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 08:58:10 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/19-oct-2020-moment/</guid>
      <description>-
quay lại quán cf tôi thường lui tới thời sinh viên chợt nhận thấy hình ảnh cũ của tôi ngồi ở góc bàn quen thuộc đó cả hai đều gọi một loại thức uống, thứ cà phê vừa chua lại ngọt, ngụm một hơi và nhìn ra cơn mưa nặng trĩu của những ngày giá rét, bão bùng
và hai ánh mắt bắt gặp nhau, mỉm cười dường như đã hiểu ra một vài điều, được tôi luyện thêm một ít và thì thầm với nhau điều gì đó</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># những đôi mắt</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/11-oct-2020-eyes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 08:57:25 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/11-oct-2020-eyes/</guid>
      <description>-
đôi mắt vô tư hồn nhiên cậu nhóc
đôi mắt trải đời đầy kinh nghiệm cụ già
cậu nhóc hướng tới ngày mai với những chuyến đi thú vị đang chờ đón
cụ già nhìn lại quãng đời mình cũng những kỷ niệm khó quên
đôi mắt đầu con đường
đôi mắt cuối con đường
cả hai đều có một điểm chung
một nụ cười, tự nhiên, từ tâm hồn</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># sẽ ra sao</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/05-oct-2020-randomness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 08:56:52 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/05-oct-2020-randomness/</guid>
      <description>-
ký ức có tốt có xấu
tốt nhiều thì sao
xấu nhiều sẽ như thế nào
ngồi trời đổ cơn mưa
cơn mưa như gột rửa mọi thứ
mọi điều tốt điều xấu
để chỗ cho những điều tốt xấu khác
hy vọng lần này
tốt nhiều hơn xấu
nhưng cũng chẳng bận tâm
mưa rồi cũng sẽ đến
quan trọng là người giữ
những cảm giác lúc bấy giờ</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># quote reading 1</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/30-sep-2020-quote-reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 08:55:37 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/30-sep-2020-quote-reading/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Kẻ bộ hành&amp;rdquo;
Tôi sẽ kể bạn nghe câu chuyện về một người lạ, người mà tôi gọi là “kẻ bộ hành”.
Kẻ bộ hành là người luôn muốn đi tìm kiếm, nhưng tìm điều gì thì anh vẫn chưa hình dung được, bởi không phải anh sẽ tìm một người nào, hay một cái gì cụ thể… Và rồi, kẻ bộ hành cũng không cần phải biết điều mà anh ta muốn tìm kiếm, vì đơn giản rằng cuộc đời của mỗi người chính là một hành trình tìm kiếm bản thân…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># đèn vàng</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/20-sep-2020-yellow-light/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 08:49:59 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/20-sep-2020-yellow-light/</guid>
      <description>-
giữa những căn nhà đèn trắng lại có căn nhà đèn vàng tại sao lại đèn vàng? phải chăng là để cho tôi chú ý là do đèn vàng giá thấp, dịu mắt hơn, lựa chọn cho sự hoài niệm hay là cặp đôi nào đó đang mặn nồng trong không gian ấm áp đó
hay muốn nổi trội hơn, khác biệt với đám đông đèn trắng như thể đứa trẻ la hét đòi sự chú ý hay chỉ vì lý đơn giản là chủ nhà thích</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># lắc lư</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/15-sep-2020-timepiece/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 11:11:07 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/15-sep-2020-timepiece/</guid>
      <description>-
Sẽ có những lúc mà đứng cũng thấy mỏi, ngồi cũng chẳng yên, nằm cũng thấy muộn phiền, mỗi cơ bắp thớ thịt trong người cũng như đang biểu tình chống đối không cho làm một hành động nào cả. Làm những việc mình thích không còn là lựa chọn nữa. Người mình yêu thương cũng bỗng nhiên thành người dưng.
Mọi thứ đều cảm thấy bất an. Mọi câu nói, mọi lời truyền cảm hứng cũng ko có tác động.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># người quen cũ</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/08-sep-2020-old-acquaintance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 11:02:34 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/08-sep-2020-old-acquaintance/</guid>
      <description>-
Gã từng là con người thuộc dạng dễ bị lay động, đùn đẩy khiến gã không thể làm gì bởi gã quá ngoan hiền. Nhận ra điều đó khiến gã buồn, chán nản và thất vọng nhưng gã đã cải thiện được điều đó. Gã nói tôi rằng cái phiên bản đó của gã không còn nữa nhưng đôi lúc gã vẫn cảm nhận được nó ở đâu đó trong tâm gã.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># hz</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/06-sep-2020-hz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 16:36:56 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/06-sep-2020-hz/</guid>
      <description>-
mỗi ng như một cơn sóng, tần số dao động, một giai điệu khác nhau và độc nhất
hoà quyện cùng những người khác, phù hợp, giao hưởng, hoà âm tạo thành một bài ca tuyệt vời, đằm thắm, sâu sắc
thế nhưng có những người bản thân họ cũng đã là một bản hoà âm, chỉ có thể ngân nga khi đứng một mình, họ biết điều đó, chấp nhận nó nên rồi cũng không còn quan trọng việc được hoà quyện</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># quán cf</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/04-sep-2020-cf-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 16:33:08 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/04-sep-2020-cf-shop/</guid>
      <description>-
Tôi ưa chuộng những nơi như thế này, ko quá cầu kì lại cực kì đơn giản, dù không mở nhạc như nơi khác mà lại đủ âm thanh, thứ tiếng, tiếng của mọi loại xe qua lại, tiếng người rôm rả chia sẻ về cuộc đời họ, tiếng kêu leng keng của chìa khoá treo trước bụng của mấy doanh nhân, tiếng chân chạy ình ịch của những gã đang cố giảm cân và tiếng phì phèo điếu thuốc của cụ già với cái nhìn xa xăm&amp;hellip; Âm thanh của cuộc sống.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># Force Positivity</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/26-aug-2020-force-positivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 20:58:46 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/26-aug-2020-force-positivity/</guid>
      <description>-
I struggle with happiness..
I think we all do.. and I don&amp;rsquo;t think a lot of people talk about it because&amp;hellip; There&amp;rsquo;s no in between!
I think it&amp;rsquo;s either you&amp;rsquo;re happy or you&amp;rsquo;re depressed! But what if you&amp;rsquo;re just fine?
There&amp;rsquo;s times where I feel really happy but at that time I also know this is temporary and I&amp;rsquo;m gonna go back to just fine. And there&amp;rsquo;s times where I feel unhappy and I know it&amp;rsquo;s gonna go back to normal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># Captain of a ship</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/24-aug-2020-captain-of-a-ship/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 06:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/24-aug-2020-captain-of-a-ship/</guid>
      <description>-
&amp;ldquo;Cái anh thiếu là đồng minh&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
Có người nói tôi như thế, khen tôi có nhiều ý tưởng, hay ho, tuy không quá mới nhưng đáng để thực hiện nhưng lại chê tôi quá cô độc và khuyên nhủ rằng thế giới này muốn tiến xa hơn thì phải có bạn đồng hành.
Tôi thấy một phần nào đó nó lung lay được mình vì hồi đó giờ trên con thuyền này chỉ có tôi làm thuyền trưởng, điều hành mọi thứ nên vì vậy nó đi khá chậm so với mặt bằng chung.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title># Sputnik thoughts</title>
      <link>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/22-aug-2020-sputnik-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 16:13:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://halfasmoke.onrender.com/posts/22-aug-2020-sputnik-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>-
&amp;hellip;dưới đây là trích đoạn:
Tất cả những gì tôi có là - tôi. Lúc nào cũng vậy
Chưa bao giờ mình có thể đắm trong cái thế giới của những sắc thái bất thường, thoáng qua này
Trong mọi chuyện chúng ta nghĩ là đã hiểu toàn bộ vẫn luôn ẩn giấu chừng ấy những điều chúng ta chưa hiểu
Sự hiểu biết chẳng là gì ngoài tổng số những sự hiểu nhầm của chúng ta</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
